{"experimentVersion":"mturk2D_peanutmartini","participantID":"","participantAge":"","participantGender":0,"confirmationCode":"0247987","participantFeedback":"","transferCounterbalance":true,"intermingledTrials":false,"totalTrials":77,"dataRecordFrequency":0.05999999865889549,"restbreakDuration":30.0,"getReadyDuration":5.0,"totalExperimentTime":0.0,"trialList":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,20,21,22,23,24,25,26,27,28,29,30,31,32,33,34,35,36,37,38,39,40,41,42,43,44,45,46,47,48,49,50,51,52,53,54,55,56,57,58,59,60,61,62,63,64,65,66,67,68,69,70,71,72,73,74,75,76],"allTrialData":[{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[0],"mapName":"Persistent","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[0.0],"totalMovementTime":[0.0],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[false],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[false],"FLAG_frameRateError":[false],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"InformationScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"BeforeStartingScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"ConsentScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"StartScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"InstructionsScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"pineapple","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"pineapple","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"GetReady","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-4.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-4.0,"y":2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-2.0,"y":2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"RestBreak","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-2.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-2.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-2.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"RestBreak","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":4.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":1.0,"y":2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-2.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-4.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":4.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":4.0,"y":2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":4.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-4.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-4.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-4.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-2.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"RestBreak","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":4.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":-3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_martini","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"martini","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-4.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-1.0,"y":-4.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":3.0,"y":2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-2.0,"y":-2.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-2.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":-3.0,"y":3.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"FourRooms_peanut","doubleRewardTask":true,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"peanut","bridgeStates":[true,true,true,true],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":2.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0}],"presentPositions":[{"x":-1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":-1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":-1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0},{"x":1.0,"y":1.0,"z":0.0}],"maxMovementTime":50.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Exit","doubleRewardTask":false,"freeForage":false,"rewardType":"","bridgeStates":[],"debriefQuestion":{"questionText":"","stimulus":"","answers":[]},"debriefResponse":"","debriefResponseTime":0.0,"playerSpawnLocation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"playerSpawnOrientation":{"x":0.0,"y":0.0,"z":0.0},"rewardPositions":[],"presentPositions":[],"maxMovementTime":0.0,"trialScore":0.0,"firstMovementTime":[],"totalMovementTime":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.30000001192092898,"preRewardAppearTime":0.30000001192092898,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":1.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"hallwayFreezeTime":5.0,"preFreezeTime":0.30000001192092898,"oneSquareMoveTime":0.20000000298023225,"minTimeBetweenMoves":0.3499999940395355,"blankTime":2.0,"animationTime":1.0,"FLAG_cliffFallError":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[],"FLAG_dataWritingError":[],"FLAG_fullScreenModeError":[],"FLAG_frameRateError":[],"stateTransitions":[],"timeStepTrackingData":[],"giftWrapStateTransitions":[]}]}